7art-screensavers.com 2015-12-29

# 7art-screensavers - free clock screensavers and live animated wallpapers

**Collection and Use of your Personal Information**   
Any personal information that you provide to our web site shall stay absolutely safe, private, and secure. We do not resell personal information to outside sources. We may use your information to inform you about products or services offered by us and our partners. When placing an order, our e-commerce provider will handle your personal information and keep it absolutely safe, private and secure. In fact, even we cannot access your credit card information. 

**Security of your Personal Information**   
We have taken the appropriate steps and followed industry standards to secure any personal data stored by our systems. 

**Bundled Software**   
Free 7art screensavers (but not the commercial ones) usually come with bundled software from reliable respected companies. You can always uninstall this third party software easily after the installation. For details please read the disclosure text in the beginning of the installation of each free screensaver. Bundling with other software lets us to keep the majority of our screensavers free of charge. 

**Cookies**   
We may use cookies to store information about your visits to improve the use of our websites. In addition, during the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Google use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads based on visit to this sites and/or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page!](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) We do not use cookies to store personal information such as your name and do not retrieve any information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. You can always disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer. 

**IP Addresses**   
We may also collect your IP address for safety and security purposes. An IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet. 

**Log Files**   
Other non-personal information collected in the form of logs - files that record website activity, including how many hits a particular web page is getting. This entries enable us to assess overall site activity, track interest in advertised sales, track interest in purchase behavior, and troubleshoot technical concerns. Through the use of log files, we may also collect certain demographic information such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer, Firefox), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows XP or Mac OS), and the domain name of your Internet service provider. 

**Email Newsletter**   
Our newsletter is strictly run as an "opt-out" newsletter. We never send unsolicited emails. Information gathered during voluntary newsletter subscription is restricted to email address. This information is used solely by 7ART-SCREENSAVERS and will not be sold to, or used by, any third party. We will only use this information for sending the regular newsletter about product updates and new releases. 

**Credit Card Transactions**   
We do not store any credit card information (name on credit card, credit card number and expiry date) for any purchase made on our site. 

**External Links**   
Our site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We encourage our users to read third party sites' privacy policies before submitting personal information. 

**Your Choices** You may unsubscribe from our e-mail list. You may direct us not to share your e-mail with our partners for offers of their products and services. You may also turn off cookies in your browser.   

**Contact Information**   
We welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Statement. If you have questions about this Statement or believe that we have not adhered to it, please please e-mail us using our [contact webpage.](http://7art-screensavers.com/support.shtml)

By using this site, you signify your assent to the 7ART-SCREENSAVERS Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this site. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Please check back from time to time to ensure that you are aware of these changes. Your continued use of this site will signify your acceptance of these changes. 

The products on this site utilize InstallMonetizer.com software recommendation platform. This valuable service helps us earn money which in turns helps us pay for resources such as server costs, product research, development, marketing, etc. Our goal is to develop amazing software for you our users at zero or low cost. 

**Overview** :   
InstallMonetizer is a software recommendation platform that enables software developers to recommend other software during installation of their application. Install Monetizer helps users discover other software and in exchange the software developers earn commission for facilitating this service. Recommendations for various software advertisers appear as full window advertorials. Only selected high quality advertisers are shown. 

**Quality of Products Installed** :   
Advertisers working with InstallMonetizer monetize from the installs we provide in various methods (from search updates, coupons to freemium products). They review each product through quality assurance before it is released. However, they recommend the software developer and end users to review the recommended software product, its privacy and terms before engaging with that advertiser. This is the same sort of engagement every user should do when installing any software Other quality checks: - recommendations are only shown during installing of the software developers product. No additional advertisers are recommended post install. - users have the chance to accept or decline each offer. They are shown a description of the product and links to all privacy and terms for each advertiser. 

**Benefits of working with InstallMonetizer** :   
Software developers need to generate money. They have to support their costs in server costs, product research, development, marketing and more. To cover their costs, they can either charge their users a cost to access their software products, or provide their software for free if end users try our recommended advertiser software. Most users want free software so Install Monetizer recommendation platform the preferred method in which software developers generate money. 

**Privacy** :   
Install Monetizer values the privacy. They are committed to ethical delivery advertising recommendation and delivery of recommended products. They do not collect any personally identifiable information. In simple language this means, they do not know the name, gender, age, email, and interests of any users. To read their privacy policy in full, please find it below. In additional, each advertiser product recommended has its own privacy policy which each user can freely review before accepting any recommended product. 

**Privacy Policy for InstallMonetizer** :   
Install Monetizer herein referred to as ("We" or "Install Monetizer") regards each user privacy as important. This privacy policy covers the privacy rules associated with user interaction with Install Monetizer websites, services or products and recommended advertiser which are presented to end users via other partner software products. User must review the partner software product own privacy policy and in addition review the privacy policy of any advertiser product recommended by Install Monetizer. *Partner software product are third party software developers who have chosen to display recommended advertiser software via Install Monetizer platform. 

**WHAT WE COLLECT AND WHY** : We collection information to help ensure the products we recommend are compatible with user pc specifications. When a user begins installation of a partner software product, Installmonetizer downloads a small file which determines the specifications of a computer, language, software & browsers on the user pc, country level location of a user, and verification of any recommended advertiser the user installed. No personally identifiable information is gathered. While visiting our websites, we may send your browser a cookie which is stored in your browser and allows us to identify it. Cookies are used too help better understand our users product interest. In addition, our websites include traffic tracking software which simply tracks the number of visits to our sites and usage of our site. USAGE OF COLLECTED DATA: Any information collect is anonymous. We use the data in whole to improve our advertiser recommendations. We do not sell or otherwise market this information to third parties. We may from time to time share with advertisers non-personally identifiable information for them to improve the performance of their products. 

We may share information if required to: (1) comply with law, regulation, subpoena or court order; (2) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (3) enforce this Privacy Policy and/or any other agreements between you and Install Monetizer, including investigation of potential violations thereof; or (4) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Install Monetizer, its visitors, users and/or the public. 

**INFORMATION SECURITY** : We use industry standard encryption and security protocols to ensure the data collected is secure. Although no technology is 100% secure we strive to use the best technology to protect our data. That being said, despite the measures we take we cannot warrant the security of any information provided to us. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time. 

If you have feedback, questions or concerns contact us at Privacy, c/o Install Monetizer 5655 Silver Creek Vly Rd 615 San Jose, CA 95138. You may also email us atsupport@installmonetizer.com
